Cuz you know, Candace Owens right out
outside right now, and she's scared.
>> I don't know her, but I
have no fear.
>> You don't know Candace Owens?
>> No.
Who is that?
>> You've never heard of Candace Owens?
>> Mhm.
>> Are you bucking me right now?
>> I don't know who that is.
>> Your Your messages are very similar, so
I'm shocked to see that. I mean,
granted, she's She's married to a white
man. However,
>> are similar?
>> Uh yeah, but she's married to a white
man.
>> Our messages are similar?
>> Um
She's going up against the same people
you're going up against. She's trying to
educate people.
>> know who that is, but I'm pretty sure
that if we were similar, we would be in
alignment.
>> Want you to say I'm being messy with
this clip when it go viral when I asked
you about Candace Owens, and you're
like, "Who is that?" That alone is going
to I ain't got nothing to do with this.
I just asked the question because